So over here, let's see what we have.
Let's get started with a simple question.
So I want to ask perplexity about the difference it provides
with the other AI tools out there, right?
So I want to ask, hey, perplexity, what are you?
Are you a chatbot?
AI chatbot.
And what is your difference with a tool like chat GPT, right?
So this is the question I want to ask.
And I send my command.
It goes through a deep search or something like that.
I can wait until I get my answer.
Publicity is an AI answer engine, right?
An assistant that uses large language models together
with live web search and key differences with chat GPT.
So perplexity is an answer engine focused on web search, web
research and fact finding while chat GPT is a general
purpose conversational model, right?
So we cannot have a conversation with perplexity.
And as I mentioned at the very beginning of this lecture,
this is a tool when it comes to professional researchers and
fact-based researchers.
And when we want accurate answers and, you know,
we're not looking forward to have a conversation or anything
like that with an artificial intelligence, right?
When we're looking for data, when we're looking for information,
just like what we do with Google, right?
But perplexity is an AI Google.
So it's a mixture of artificial intelligence and search engines,
as I said.
Yep, it's very useful when it comes to scientific stuff,
et cetera.